Guide to the George Borchardt Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII
  - Authors and Agents, A-Y
    - Timerman, Jacob: 1982 -- Timerman, Jacob: Movie Rights -- Thomas, Audrey: 1984 -- Toys to Make -- Tucker, William: 1984 -- Tuten, Frederick: 1979-1988 (Box 384)
    - Ubell, Al -- Victor, Thomas: 1980-1985 -- Warner, Dennis: 1977 -- Watson, Robert: 1981 -- Weidenfeld: Young Historian -- Wheeler, Gordon: 1986 -- Weisel, Elie: Foreign Rights -- Wiseman, Thomas: 1980 -- Wrighton, Patricia: Hutchinson: 1985 -- Writer's Guild of America -- Yurick, Sol: 1984-1985 (Box 385)
- Series VIII
  - Authors and Agents, A-Y
    - Abrams, Linsey: 1981 -- Aksyonov, Vassily: 1983-1985 -- Asprey, Robert: 1980 (Box 386)
    - Astrachan, Anthony: 1979-1982 -- Azrin, Nathan: 1980, 1982 -- Balcells: 1989 -- Berg, Barbara: 1982, 1984 (Box 387)
    - Bernabo: 1988: A-F -- (Italy): 1989: G-Z, 1990: A-Z -- Bing, Elizabeth: 1982-1984 (Box 388)
    - Bing, Elizabeth: 1985 -- Bloom, Marc: 1982, 1987-1988 -- Blonsky, Marshall: 1981, 1985 -- Bly, Carol: 1981-1982 -- Booth, Stanley: 1984-1985 -- Busworth, David: 1982-1983 (Box 389)
    - Bowers, John: 1979-1983 -- Brazil, Karin Schindler: 1990 -- Brolin, Brent: 1985 -- Burkholz, Herbert: 1985 -- Butterworth, Michael: 1984 (Box 390)
    - Carlisle, Olga: 1979 -- Caute, David: 1985 -- Chanoff, David -- Charyn, Jerome: 1982 -- Chowder, Ken: 1987 -- Collier, Christopher: 1981-1983 -- Collier, James: 1986-1987 -- Connell, Maureen: 1981-1985 (Box 391)
    - Danton, Arthur: 1981-1984 -- Drexler, Rosalyn: 1983-1984 -- Dunn, Robert: 1983-1985 -- Epstein, Joseph: 1983 -- The English Agency (Japan): 1990, 1987 -- Ettinger, Elzbieta: 1980-1981, 1984-1985 (Box 392)
    - Fackenheim, Emil: 1983 -- Falk, Candace: 1983-1984 -- Ferrorelli and Starr -- Freedman, Ralph: 1983 -- French General: Translators, etc.: 1989 -- Friedman, Maurice: 1984-1985 -- Gerd Plessl: Eastern Europe: 1986, other (Box 393)
    - Hofman, Paul: 1982 -- Hoffman, Robert: 1988 -- Howard, Bob: 1981-1984 -- Hyman, Mary and Philip: 1981 -- Insdorff, Annette: 1980-1983 (Box 394)
    - Jacoby, Susan: 1980, 1986 -- Japan Uni: 1989, 1990 -- Tuttle-Mori: 1990 -- Jorant, Albert: 1981 -- Jovan Milenkovich (Eastern Europe): 1986-- (Box 395)
    - Kaplan, Fred: 1984-1985 -- Katz, Steve: 1984-1985 -- Keeble, John: 1980 -- Kramer, Hilton: 1980-1983 -- Kramer, Mark: 1982 -- Kreiger, Barbara: 1980-1982 (Box 396)
    - Lahr, John: 1980-1981 -- Lapautre: (France): 1990: E-L -- Lapautre: 1989: N-Z (Box 397)
    - Lapautre: (France): 1990 -- Lapautre: (France): Financial and General: 1990 -- Lawner, Lynne: 1984-1985 -- Lebowitz, Albert: 1983-1984 -- Mohrbooks: 1989: A-H (Box 398)
    - Mohrbooks: 1989: I-Z, 1990: A-Z (Germany) -- Molinaro, Ursule: 1985 -- Noren, Catherine: 1979 -- Nunez, Singrid: 1978-1985 (Box 399)
    - Old Permissions -- Portugal, R. de la Concha: 1988 -- Raphael, Chaim: 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 400)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: 1989: A-Z -- Simon, Richard Scott: General/Miscellaneous: 1989 (Box 401)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: (UK): 1990: A-Z (Box 402)
    - Sane, Lennart: 1989: A-Z -- (Scandinavia): 1990: A-Z -- Schindler: 1989 -- Spain: Balcells: 1990: A-Z (Box 403)
    - T&L: 1989: A-Z -- (Holland): 1990: A-Z -- Rombach: 1989 -- Tuttle-Mori: 1989 -- Wildavski, Aaron: 1981 -- Wright, Richard: 1977-1980 -- Yale University: 1981 (Box 404)
- Series IX
  - Authors and Agents, A-Z
    - AAR: Correspondence: 1991-1992 -- Adams, Jane: 1981 -- Aksyonov, Vassily: Publicity -- 1986-1987 (Box 405)
    - American Read: 1979 -- American Authors Pending: 1975 -- Atlas, James: 1982-1984 -- Azrin, Nathan: 1983-1984 (Box 406)
    - Barrett, Nicholas: Watt: 1984 -- Batchelor, John Calvin: Publicity -- Berg, Barbara: 1985 -- Boyd, Blanche: 1982 -- Botsforth, Keith -- Burkholz, Herbert: 1984 -- Caute, David: 1986 -- Chanoff, David: 1986 (Box 407)
    - Chanoff, David: 1984-1985 -- Colville, John: Watt, A.P.: 1985 -- Chesterson, G.K.: Watt, A.P.: 1986 -- Chowder, Ken: 1988 -- Cruz, Victor -- Cunningham, Anne-Marie: 1986 (Box 408)
    - Dennison, George: 1983-1985 -- Des Pres, Terrence: 1981 -- Dillon, Ellis: 1985-1990 -- Drawings: Beck, other -- Elliott, George P. (Box 409)
    - Falk, Candace: Reviews: 1984-1985 -- Feakes -- Fonda and Delyser: Correspondence with Authors and S&S: 1982, 1984 -- Fonda: Foreign and Entourage: 1982 (Box 410)
    - Fonda: Foreign and Entourage: 1987 -- Flam, Jack: 1982 -- Freedman, Ralph: 1981-1982 -- Friedman, Maurice: 1986 -- Gascar, Pierre -- Goldberg, Gerald Jay: 1980 -- Gordon, Suzanne: 1984-1985 (Box 411)
    - Hofman, Paul: 1984 -- Horowitz, David: 1979-1980 -- Hughes, Patrick: 1982 -- Hunt, Morton: 1985 -- Hyman, Mary and Philip: 1983-1985 (Box 412)
    - Insdorff, Annette: 1984-1985 -- Israel, Peter: 1983-1985 -- Jacoby, Susan: 1985 -- Jennings, Humphrey: Watt, A.P.: 1985 -- Jerome, John: 1980-1982 -- Katz, Jacob: 1985 (Box 413)
    - Keeble, John: 1982 -- Kluger, Richard: 1980 -- Korea -- Ladenis, Nico: Watt, A.P.: 1988 -- Lawner, Lynne: 1987-1988 -- Macoby, Hyam: Watt, A.P.: 1987 -- McElroy, Joseph: 1982 -- Madden, David: 1982, 1985, 1989 (Box 414)
    - Maimon, Alex -- Maks, Michelle: 1983 -- Malcolm, Janet: thru 1981 -- Malcolm, Janet: Publicity -- Mariac, Francois: The Egoists -- Matute, Anna Maria -- Mellow, James: 1986 -- Mossinsohn, Yigal (Box 415)
    - Newman, Charles: 1976 -- Perera, Victor -- Photographs: Pablo Picasso, other -- Parkes, James -- Podhoretz, Norman: 1982-1983 -- Rechy, John: 1979 (Box 416)
    - Rodriguez, Juan -- Reich, Walter: 1980 -- Rognier, Gilbert -- Rubenstein, Richard: 1975, 1980 -- Rubenstein/Katzaris: 1979 -- Rule, Jane: 1983 -- Sachs, Betsy: 1987 -- Sayre, Nora: 1979 (Box 417)
    - Sayre, Nora: 1983 -- Schwartz, Paul Waldo: 1973-1974 -- Sereny, Gitta: 1977, 1980 -- Serguine, Jaques -- Singer, Dorothy and Jerome: 1982 -- Sitney, P. Adams: 1979 -- Sowell, Thomas: 1981-1982 (Box 418)
    - Sowell, Thomas: 1983 -- Stein and Day -- Stern, Daniel: 1978-1980 -- Sulivan, Jean -- Valliere, James T. -- Voinovich, Vladimir: 1981 -- What-a-Mess: Watt, A.P. -- Mossinsohn, Yigal -- Zeiss, Antonette and Robert (Box 419)